http://www.wcoconcerts.org/privacy-policy

Contact UsWCO NewsDonate NowWisconsin Chamber Orchestra
Concerts & TicketsEvent CalendarWCO LiveWinter Chamber SeriesMasterworks SeriesConcerts on the SquareBrookfieldSpecial PerformancesEvent ArchivePlan Your VisitGetting HereWhat to ExpectEducationYoung Artist Concerto CompetitionWYSO Side by Side ProjectFamily SeriesSuper StringsMeet the WCOMusiciansMusic DirectorStaffBoard of DirectorsHistoryCoucherto SeriesAuditionsCareersSupportDonate NowFriends of the WCOIndividual Giving2020 MerchandiseBusiness SupportVolunteerWisconsin Chamber Orchestra
Concerts & TicketsOverviewEvent CalendarWCO LiveWinter Chamber SeriesMasterworks SeriesConcerts on the SquareBrookfieldSpecial PerformancesEvent ArchivePlan Your VisitOverviewGetting HereWhat to ExpectEducationOverviewYoung Artist Concerto CompetitionWYSO Side by Side ProjectFamily SeriesSuper StringsMeet the WCOOverviewMusiciansMusic DirectorStaffBoard of DirectorsHistoryCoucherto SeriesAuditionsCareersSupportOverviewDonate NowFriends of the WCOIndividual Giving2020 MerchandiseBusiness SupportVolunteer
Donate Now
Get Tickets
Become a Friend of the WCO
WCO News
ContactPrivacy PolicyEffective date: May 11, 2020Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://wcoconcerts.org website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.DefinitionsService. Service is the https://wcoconcerts.org website operated by Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc.Personal Data. Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).Usage Data. Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).Cookies. Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).Data Controller. Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.Data Processors (or Service Providers). Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.Data Subject (or User). Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USEWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email AddressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage DataWe may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.Usage DataWe may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers, and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information. Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.To provide and maintain our ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer supportTo gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our ServiceTo monitor the usage of our ServiceTo detect, prevent, and address technical issuesTo provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services, and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such informationWe need to perform a contract with youYou have given us permission to do soThe processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rightsFor payment processing purposesTo comply with the lawTo comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc.To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilityThe right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. relied on your consent to process your personal information.USE OF DATAWisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. uses the collected data for various purposes:LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL DATA UNDER GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. may process your Personal Data because:RETENTION OF DATAWisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.TRANSFER OF DATAYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.DISCLOSURE OF DATALEGAL REQUIREMENTSWisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:SECURITY OF DATAThe security of your data is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.YOUR DATA PROTECTION RIGHTS UNDER GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra, Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).SERVICE PROVIDERSWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. PAYMENTSWe may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.The payment processors we work with are:Authorize.netTheir Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/Blackbaud Merchant ServicesTheir Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.blackbaud.com/company/privacy-policy/north-americaStripeTheir Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://stripe.com/privacySquareTheir Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://squareup.com/help/us/en/article/3796-privacy-and-securityLINKS TO OTHER SITESOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.CHILDREN'S PRIVACYOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.CONTACT USIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: wco@wcoconcerts.orgBy visiting this page on our website: https://wcoconcerts.org/privacyBy phone number: 608.257.0638By mail: 321 E. Main Street, Madison, WI 53703
Get Tickets
Become a Friend of the WCO
WCO News
ContactWCO Mailing AddressWisconsin Chamber Orchestra
P.O. Box 171
Madison, WI 53701-0171WCO Office321 E. Main Street
Madison, WI 53703
—
M-F: 9:00 AM - 4:00 PMMadison, WI — Overture Center for the Arts201 State Street
Madison, WI 53703Brookfield, WI
— Sharon Lynne Wilson Center for the Arts3270 Mitchell Park Drive
Brookfield, WI 53045Your gift makes concerts possible.
Donate NowStay Close to the WCOSign up for email updates from the Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra.
Follow the WCO
©2020
Wisconsin Chamber Orchestra
Privacy & Terms
